http://www.pqc.edu/privacy-policy/

Paul Quinn College’s Commitment to Privacy
The privacy of visitors to our web sites is very important to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information received, collected, and used by Paul Quinn College through its website.
The college adheres to legal requirements prescribed by relevant statutes, such as FERPA (the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act) of 1974. Our FERPA document notice may be found online.
This privacy policy should be considered a baseline standard. The privacy policies of individual Paul Quinn College departments may provide standards that are more rigorous or restrictive.
1) INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM WEBSITE VISITORS
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is information that can be used to identify, contact, or locate an individual, either alone or combined with other information. PII includes data such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number, or any other information that is not otherwise publicly available. The PII that Paul Quinn College collects from you is information that you supply to us, for purposes such as making a donation, completing a purchase, requesting admissions information or applying for admission.
Aggregate Data
Like other websites, Paul Quinn College’s site make use of log or session files. This is information automatically collected from you each time you visit our site. Log files typically include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. None of this information, individually or grouped together—referred to in total as “aggregate data”—will be used to identify a specific individual.
2) HOW WE USE INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM WEB VISITORS
PII and/or aggregate data collected by Paul Quinn College’s site may be used for the following:
* Educational and/or research purposes;
* Editorial and feedback purposes;
* Promotional and recruiting purposes, including soliciting philanthropic contributions and contacting prospective students;
* Statistical analysis of usage trends;
* Administration of the site;
* Gathering of demographic information;
* Website page/content and layout customization.
In addition, names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers provided by visitors via online forms may be added to Paul Quinn College’s databases. This information may be used for correspondence, e-mail, or other uses consistent with Paul Quinn College’s business practices and/or academic mission. Paul Quinn College may also use such information to provide users with notifications concerning College and community events.
3) COOKIES
Cookies are small pieces of data automatically stored in a user’s browser when a website is visited. Paul Quinn College may place cookies on a visitor’s computer to store information about visitor preferences, record user-specific information on pages accessed or visited, customize web page content based on
browser type or device, or to present visitors with content or advertisements about Paul Quinn College on other web pages they subsequently visit.
Users can set their browsers to receive notification when a web site sends them a cookie so they may accept or reject it. Note that some parts of the College web site may not function properly, or may be considerably slower, if cookies are rejected.
Third-Party Use of Cookies
Paul Quinn College’s site may place specialized coding on web pages that allows a third party to insert a cookie into a visitor’s browser. These are used for the purposes of presenting a visitor with online advertisements about Paul Quinn College after leaving our site.
When you use Paul Quinn College’s site, a third-party vendor may automatically receive your IP address. This aggregate information is used to deliver tailored advertising content about Paul Quinn College, and to measure the effectiveness of advertisements.
A third-party vendor may also collect aggregate information about the number of Paul Quinn College advertisements viewed and the number of times users click on the advertisements. This type of information is used to track the success of these advertisements, but cannot be used to identify users in any way. (Note: Paul Quinn College’s privacy policy does not apply to, nor can we control the activities of, other advertisers or web sites.)
Users may control third-party cookies via their web browser preference settings. Users may also opt out of the use of third-party cookies, in general, by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. As with the College website, other websites may not function properly, or may be considerably slower, if cookies are rejected.
4) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA TO THIRD PARTIES
Paul Quinn College occasionally retains the services of third parties to process information or financial transactions. Before providing PII to a third party, Paul Quinn College will obtain a non-disclosure and confidentiality agreement from the third party. Aggregate data and/or information that is publicly available is not subject to such agreements. We will disclose personal information when required by law, judicial process, warrant, or subpoena.
5) OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY
Paul Quinn College is firmly committed to data security. To restrict unauthorized access and to ensure data integrity and security, Paul Quinn College implements physical, electronic, and administrative policies and procedures intended to safeguard information the College collects and/or stores. However, the College cannot assure or warrant absolute data security.
6) CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Paul Quinn College does not deliberately collect, or attempt to collect, personal information from children known to be under the age of thirteen (13). The College cannot always determine, however, if a visitor is a child. In general, the subject matter provided on the College’s web site is not directed toward children under the age of thirteen (13).
7) YOUR CONSENT & HOW TO CONTACT US
By visiting Paul Quinn College sites and services, you consent to the collection, storage, and dissemination of PII and aggregate data as described above. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time.
Effective Date
This policy was updated on December 10, 2014 and is reviewed annually.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact the Information Technology Department at helpdesk@pqc.edu
Filing a Sexual Misconduct Complaint (Title IX)
© 2014 Paul Quinn College. All Rights Reserved.
‹
›
×
